<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CSIS</string>
    <string name="title"><![CDATA[Computer Science & Information Systems]]></string>
    <string name="faculty">Faculty</string>
    <string name="choBiography">
        Il-Hyung Cho is an associate professor and chair of the Department of Computer Science at
        Saginaw Valley State University, Michigan, where he has been since 2003. During 2010-2011
        he was a Visiting Professor of Bioinformatics lab at Washington State University. He
        received a B.E. in Electronic &amp; Computer Engineering from Yonsei University in 1987, and
        an M.S. in Computer Science from Bowling Green State University. He received his Ph.D. in
        Computer Science from Clemson University in 2000. He worked at Iona Technologies in Boston
        as a software engineer in 2000-2001, and at Clemson University as visiting lecturer in
        2001-2003. \n\nHis research interests center on object oriented system design, distributed object systems,
        software engineering, bioinfomatics tools development, and computer security and forensics.
        He helped the construction of genome database for Rosaceae Crop (www.rosaceae.org/). He
        has given many talks in professional conferences and SE&amp;T colloquium, most recently at
        Oxford University (UK) on the topic of Business Innovation with User Knowledge and IT
        Technologies.
    </string>
    <string name="corserBiography">
        George Corser is an Assistant Professor of Computer Science and Information Systems (CSIS)
        at Saginaw Valley State University (SVSU). His research defines and analyzes location
        privacy and security protocols in vehicle networks. His teaching explores web and mobile
        app development, theoretical computer science and cybercrime. His professional service
        includes advisory and leadership positions in SVSU student organizations, international
        technical societies, and a cybercrime analysis consortium.
    </string>

    <string name="rahmanBiography">
        I graduated with PhD in Computational Analysis and Modeling (2013) from Louisiana Tech
        University, Ruston, USA. Prior that, I received MS and BSc in Computer Science and
        Engineering from University of Dhaka, Bangladesh in 2008 and 2006 respectively. I
        received MS in Mathematics (2011) and MS in Computer Science (2013) from Louisiana Tech
        University. Before joining SVSU in 2013, I was a research assistant from March, 2009
        to February, 2013 at Center for Secure Cyberspace at Louisiana Tech University.\n\n
        My research interests include detecting and mitigating cyber-behavioral anomalies,
        behavioral biometrics, machine learning, knowledge discovery from data, image processing
        and human activity detection from video. I am a member of IEEE and ACM.
    </string>
    <string name="show_img">Tap To Show CIS Plan Chart</string>
    <string name="show_cs_img">Tap To Show CS Plan Chart</string>
</resources>
